{
    "id": "49e90f0df3ea42b9bbe0d189e4f2db33",
    "title": "Common Idioms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not surprised that she doesn't have any friends. She is as sour as ..............................",
            "description": "If a person is as sour as vinegar, they are very disagreeable.",
            "answers": [
                "grapes",
                "vinegar",
                "tamarind"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has so many friends because she is as sweet as ................................",
            "description": "If you are as sweet as honey, you are a very sweet person.",
            "answers": [
                "milk",
                "cookies",
                "honey"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't have a sweet ......................... I rarely eat desserts.",
            "description": "To have a sweet tooth is to have a love for sugary foods.",
            "answers": [
                "tongue",
                "mouth",
                "tooth"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I appreciate his integrity and honesty. He is a .............................. of the earth type person.",
            "description": "This is an expression used to refer to sincere and decent people.",
            "answers": [
                "salt",
                "sugar",
                "spice"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest book is selling like .................................",
            "description": "If something sells like hotcakes, it sells quickly.",
            "answers": [
                "hot potatoes",
                "hot cakes",
                "hot buns"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You should have just told me the truth. There was no need to ............................... it.",
            "description": "To sugarcoat is to present bad news in such a way that it sounds less unpleasant.",
            "answers": [
                "frame",
                "sugarcoat",
                "sugar"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Take every piece of news you find online with a grain of ...............................",
            "description": "To take something with a pinch of salt is to view it with some skepticism.",
            "answers": [
                "salt",
                "sugar",
                "spice"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time he proved that he is worth his ...............................",
            "description": "When you are worth your salt you are competent at what you do.",
            "answers": [
                "sugar",
                "salt",
                "water"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was the .................................. of her mother's eye.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mango",
                "apple",
                "cherry"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In the end his hard work bore .................................... and he became a successful musician.",
            "description": "To bear fruit is to get favorable results.",
            "answers": [
                "flower",
                "fruit",
                "result"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car won't start again. I think I bought a ...............................",
            "description": "To buy a lemon is to buy something worthless.",
            "answers": [
                "melon",
                "lemon",
                "nut"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't compare a race car with a tiny hatchback. That is like comparing apples to ................................",
            "description": "To compare apples to oranges is to compare things that are totally different.",
            "answers": [
                "mangoes",
                "cherries",
                "oranges"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}